<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">BindaasTeam</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="invite_mail">Invite Mail</string>
    <string name="invite_message">Invite Message</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="action_friends">Add</string>
    <string name="app_contact_name">Bindaas Contacts</string>
    <string name="action_navigation">Bindaas Navigation</string>
    <string name="bindaas_welcome">Welocme to Bindaas Team </string>
    <string name="bindaas_welcome2">Start your game with Profile </string>
    <string name="playerName">Bindaas Name</string>
    <string name="bindaasName">Set Bindaas Name</string>
    <string name="bindaasName2">Show Bindaas Name</string>
    <string name="playerHint">set your name for bindaas team visibility</string>
    <string name="drawer_open"> Open Navigation Drawer </string>
    <string name="drawer_close"> Close Navigation Drawer </string>
    <string name="add_groups">Add Groups</string>
    <string name="username">UserName :</string>
    <string name="password">Password :</string>
    <string name="signup">SignUp</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="email">Email :</string>
    <string name="title_activity_request">RequestActivity</string>
    <string name="message">Enter your message...........</string>
    <string name="request">Send  Request</string>
    <string name="title_activity_response">ResponseActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_reply">ReplyActivity</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="reject">Reject</string>
    <string name="group">Group Management</string>
    <string name="title_activity_group_management">GroupManagementActivity</string>
    <string name="groupName">Name Your Group</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="title_activity_league_select">LeagueSelectActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_friends_list">FriendsListActivity</string>
    <string name="leagueName">LeagueName</string>

    <color name="red">#FF0000</color>
    <!-- <color name="blue">#0000FF</color> -->

    <string-array name="menu">
        <item>Profile</item>
        <item>Friends</item>
        <item>Team Management</item>
        <item>Group Management</item>
        <item>Friend Request</item>
        <item>Group Request</item>
        <item>How to play</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="add">Create your group</string>
    <string name="team_name">Name Your Team</string>
    <string name="mailId">Email-ID</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="playerGold">Gold</string>
    <string name="goldValue">110</string>
    <string name="playerRole">110</string>
    <string name="title_activity_group_final">GroupFinalActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_team_list_view">TeamListViewActivity</string>
    <string name="searchFreind">Type Your Friend Name</string>
    <string name="searchFriendBtn">search</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>

    <!-- This is a for Banner unit app id -->
    <string name="ad_id">  ca-app-pub-2555724076385576/9206303246</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mail">MailActivity</string>
 	<string name="remember">Remember Me</string>   
    <!-- For Email Activity -->
    
    <string name="subject">Subject:</string>
     <string name="send">Send</string>
     
    <!-- Terms and Codition titles -->
    <string name="cTitle1">1.Terms of Use: </string>
    <string name="cTitle2">2.REGISTRATION:  </string>
    <string name="cTitle3">3.DELAYS IN SERVICES: </string>
    <string name="cTitle4">4.Limitation of liability:</string>
    <string name="cTitle5">5.EQUIPMENT AND OPERATION :</string>
    <string name="cTitle6">6.INFORMATION DISCLAIMER:</string>
    <string name="cTitle7">7.Advertising Material: </string>
    <string name="cTitle8">8.INDEMNIFICATION: </string>
    <string name="cTitle9">9.CONFLICTING TERMS: </string>
    <string name="cTitle10">10.ENTIRE AGREEMENT: </string>
    <string name="cTitle11">11.International Use: </string>
    <string name="cTitle12">12.TERMINATION: </string>
    <string name="cTitle13">13.JURISDICTION: </string>

    <!-- Terms and Codition Details -->
    <string name="cond1"> By installing and using our Bindaas Team Application you are agreeing to be 
        bound by the following terms and conditions. We may change these terms and conditions at any time. 
        Your continued use of our Bindaas Team Application means that you accept any new or modified 
        terms and conditions that we come up with.
		The term \'Bindaas Team Application \' is used through this entire Terms of Use document to refer to the application, its owners and the employees and associates of the owner		refer to the application, its owners and the employees and associates of the owner
	</string>
    <string name="cond2">By registering, you certify that all information you provide, now or in the future, 
	    is accurate.
		Bindaas Team Application reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to deny you access to this 
		Bindaas Team Application or any portion thereof without notice for the following reasons (a) 
		immediately by Bindaas Team Application for any unauthorized access or use by you (b) 
		immediately by Bindaas Team Application if you assign or transfer (or attempt the same) any 
		rights granted to you under this Agreement; (c) immediately, if you violate any of the other terms 
		and conditions of this User Agreement</string>
    <string name="cond3">Neither Bindaas Team Application (including its and their directors, employees, 
        affiliates, agents, representatives or subcontractors) shall be liable for any loss or liability 
        resulting, directly or indirectly, from delays or interruptions due to electronic or mechanical 
        equipment failures, telephone interconnect problems, defects, weather, strikes, walkouts, fire, acts 
        of God, riots, armed conflicts, acts of war, or other like causes. Bindaas Team Application 
        shall have no responsibility to provide you access to Bindaas Team Application while 
        interruption of Bindaas Team Application is due to any such cause shall continue.</string>
    <string name="cond4"> You agree that the Bindaas Team Application (including its and their directors, 
        employees, affiliates, agents, representatives or subcontractors) shall not be liable for any direct, 
        special, incidental, indirect or consequential damages of any kind in connection with this agreement 
        or your use of the application, even if company has been informed in advance of the possibility of such
        damages.</string>
    <string name="cond5">You shall provide and maintain all telephone/internet and other equipment necessary 
        to use Bindaas Team Application, and the costs of any such equipment and/or telephone/internet 
        connections or use, including any applicable taxes, shall be borne solely by you. You are responsible 
        for operating your own equipment used to access Bindaas Team Application.</string>
    <string name="cond6">You acknowledge that the information provided through Bindaas Team Application 
        is compiled from sources, which are beyond the control of Bindaas Team Application Though such 
        information is recognized by the parties to be generally reliable, the parties acknowledge that 
        inaccuracies may occur and Bindaas Team Application does not warrant the accuracy or suitability 
        of the information. For this reason, as well as the possibility of human and mechanical errors and 
        other factors, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT Bindaas Team Application IS PROVIDED TO YOU ON AN "AS IS, 
        WITH ALL FAULTS" BASIS. Bindaas Team Application EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES, 
        WHETHER EXPRESS, ORAL, IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, OF ANY KIND TO THE USERS AND/OR ANY THIRD PARTY, 
        INCLUDING ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF ACCURACY, TIMELINESS, COMPLETENESS, MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS 
        FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AS WELL AS ANY WARRANTIES ARISING BY VIRTUE OF CUSTOM OF TRADE OR COURSE OF 
        DEALING AND ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF TITLE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. IN ADDITION, Bindaas Team 
        Application DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT IT WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS OR IS SUITABLE FOR 
        YOUR NEEDS.
		Under this User Agreement, you assume all risk of errors and/or omissions in Bindaas Team 
		Application, including the transmission or translation of information. You assume full responsibility 
		for implementing sufficient procedures and checks to satisfy your requirements for the accuracy and 
		suitability of Bindaas Team Application, including the information, and for maintaining any 
		means, which you may require for the reconstruction of lost data or subsequent manipulations or 
		analyses of the information under the User Agreement.
		YOU AGREE THAT Bindaas Team Application (INCLUDING ITS AND THEIR OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, 
		AFFILIATES, GROUP COMPANIES AGENTS, REPRESENTATIVES OR SUBCONTRACTORS) SHALL NOT IN ANY EVENT BE 
		LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO 
		USE Bindaas Team Application FOR ANY PURPOSE WHATSOEVER. Bindaas Team Application AND IT\'S 
		AFFILIATES, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES AND AGENTS SHALL HAVE NO LIABILITY IN TORT, CONTRACT, OR 
		OTHERWISE TO USER AND/OR ANY THIRD PARTY.</string>
    <string name="cond7">Some part of the Bindaas Team Application may contain advertising information 
        or promotional material or other material submitted to Bindaas Team Application by third parties. 
        Responsibility for ensuring that the material submitted for inclusion on Bindaas Team 
        Application complies with applicable law is exclusively on the party providing the information 
        material. Your correspondence or business dealings with, or participation in promotions of 
        advertisers or including payment and delivery of related goods or services, and any other terms, 
        conditions, warranties or representations associated with such dealings, are solely between you and 
        such advertiser. Bindaas Team Application will not be responsible or liable for any claim, 
        error, omission, inaccuracy in advertising material or any loss or damage of any sort incurred as 
        the result of any such dealings or as a result of the presence of such advertisers on the application. 
        Bindaas Team Application reserves the right to omit, suspend or change the position of any 
        advertising material submitted for insertion.</string>
    <string name="cond8"> YOU SHALL INDEMNIFY, DEFEND AND HOLD HARMLESS Bindaas Team Application 
        (INCLUDING ITS AND THEIR OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AFFILIATES, GROUP COMPANIES, AGENTS, 
        REPRESENTATIVES OR SUBCONTRACTORS) FROM ANY AND ALL CLAIMS AND LOSSES IMPOSED ON, INCURRED BY OR 
        ASSERTED AS A RESULT OF OR RELATED TO: (a) your access and use of Bindaas Team Application 
        (b) any non-compliance by user with the terms and conditions hereof; or (c) any third party actions 
        related to users receipt and use of the information, whether authorized or unauthorized. Any clause 
        declared invalid shall be deemed severable and not affect the validity or enforceability of the 
        remainder. These terms may only be amended in a writing signed by Bindaas Team Application.
</string>
    <string name="cond9"> In no event will Gender Finder be liable for any direct, indirect, special, punitive, 
        exemplary or consequential losses or damages of whatsoever kind arising out of your use or access to 
        the Application, including loss of profit or the like whether or not in the contemplation of the 
        parties, whether based on breach of contract, tort (including negligence), product liability or 
        otherwise. 
        Gender Finder is not liable to you for any damage or alteration to your equipment including but not 
        limited to computer equipment, handheld device or mobile telephones as a result of the installation 
        or use of the Application. 
		Nothing in these Appterms shall exclude or limit Gender Finder’s liability for death or personal 
		injury caused by negligence or for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation or any other liability 
		which cannot be excluded or limited under applicable law.</string>
    <string name="cond10">This User Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between the parties, and no 
        other agreement, written or oral, exists between you and Bindaas Team Application. By using 
        the Information on Bindaas Team Application, you assume full responsibility for any and all 
        gains and losses, financial, emotional or otherwise, experienced, suffered or incurred by you. 
        Bindaas Team Application does not guarantee the accuracy, completeness or timeliness of, or 
        otherwise endorse in any way, the views, opinions or recommendations expressed in the Information.
		THE SERVICE IS PROVIDED "AS IS," WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING 
		WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY WARRANTY FOR INFORMATION, DATA, SERVICES, UNINTERRUPTED ACCESS, OR PRODUCTS 
		PROVIDED THROUGH OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SERVICE. SPECIFICALLY, Bindaas Team Application 
		DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO: (i) ANY WARRANTIES CONCERNING THE 
		AVAILABILITY, ACCURACY, USEFULNESS, OR CONTENT OF INFORMATION, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES; AND (ii) ANY 
		WARRANTIES OF TITLE, WARRANTY OF NON-INFRINGEMENT, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A 
		PARTICULAR PURPOSE. THIS DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY APPLIES TO ANY DAMAGES OR INJURY CAUSED BY ANY 
		FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DELETION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR 
		TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, COMMUNICATION LINE FAILURE, THEFT OR DESTRUCTION OR UNAUTHORIZED 
		ACCESS TO, ALTERATION OF, OR USE OF RECORD, WHETHER FOR BREACH OF CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, OR 
		UNDER ANY OTHER CAUSE OF ACTION.
		NEITHER Bindaas Team Application NOR ANY OF ITS EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, SUCCESSORS, ASSIGNS, 
		AFFILIATES, GROUP COMPANIES OR CONTENT OR SERVICE PROVIDERS SHALL BE LIABLE TO YOU OR OTHER THIRD 
		PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF USE OF 
		SERVICE OR INABILITY TO GAIN ACCESS TO OR USE THE SERVICE OR OUT OF ANY BREACH OF ANY WARRANTY. 
		FURTHER, YOU AGREE AND UNDERSTAND THAT ALL SERVICES PROVIDED ARE NON-REFUNDABLE AND THAT YOU SHOULD 
		CAREFULLY CONSIDER WHETHER OUR SERVICES ARE ABLE TO MEET YOUR NEEDS.</string>
    <string name="cond11"> This Bindaas Team Application is controlled and operated from within India. 
	    Those who chose to access the Bindaas Team Application from other locations do so at their own 
	    risk and are responsible for compliance with applicable laws.</string>
    <string name="cond12">This User Agreement and the license rights granted hereunder shall remain in full 
	    force and effect unless terminated or canceled for any of the following reasons: (a) immediately by 
	    Bindaas Team Application for any unauthorized access or use by you (b) immediately by Gender 
	    Finder Play Application if you assign or transfer (or attempt the same) any rights granted to you 
	    under this Agreement; (c) immediately, if you violate any of the other terms and conditions of 
	    this User Agreement. Termination or cancellation of this Agreement shall not effect any right or 
	    relief to which Bindaas Team Application may be entitled, at law or in equity. Upon termination 
	    of this User Agreement, all rights granted to you will terminate and revert to Bindaas Team 
	    Application. Except as set forth herein, regardless of the reason for cancellation or termination of
	     this User Agreement, the fee charged if any for access to Bindaas Team Application is non-refundable 
	     for any reason.</string>
    <string name="cond13"> The terms of this agreement are exclusively based on and subject to Indian law. 
	    You hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of courts in Bangalore, India in all 
	    disputes arising out of or relating to the use of this Bindaas Team Application. Use of this 
	    Bindaas Team Application is unauthorized in any jurisdiction that does not give effect to all 
	    provisions of these terms and conditions, including without limitation this paragraph.</string>

</resources>